<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christ Community Church</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 22:57:51 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 22:57:51 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the New CCC Website!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The website has been a work in progress for many months and we are beyond excited to launch it to you all. The website has a large amount of new features! Throughout the rest of this blog post, we will speak about the purposes, uses of the website, and how you can stay up to date with community activity via the website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Online Sermons&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A major addition to the website is access to the sermon recorded every week. Under the sermon tab above, you will find a page devoted to inventory of the sermons. All you need to do is select the month you are looking for and select the sermon you would like to listen to. As the speediness of the website is of large concern for our team, we intended on moving sets of past sermons to the Soundcloud profile. Soundcloud is the web application that allows us to broadcast our sermons. So if you are looking for a specific sermon and cannot find it, follow the button to our Soundcloud profile for our extensive library of sermons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;The Blog&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Understand that the website is still very early in development and will continue expanding through user interface and functionality. If you are interested in helping continue the development of the website, even if you do not consider yourself and expert, or even mediocre at web design, feel free to email &lt;a href=&quot;cccwebtech@gmail.com&quot;&gt;cccwebtech@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 06:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2015/08/23/Hello-World!.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2015/08/23/Hello-World!.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
