<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Christ Community Church</title>
    <description>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.
</description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 09:22:00 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 09:22:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to the New CCC Website!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The website has been a work in progress for many months and we are beyond excited to launch it to you! The website has a large amount of new features compared to previous versions of the site! Throughout the rest of this blog post, we will speak about the purposes, uses of the website, and how you can stay up to date with community activity via the website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;The Purpose&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The purpose for any website in today&amp;#39;s day and age is stand brand your organization or company on the internet. While this was important to us to provide accessibility for our users, it was of utmost importance that we created an area that was welcoming and informational for our community members or nonmembers alike. We strove to provide multiple aspects, such as online sermons and blog posts, that we intend to continue to develop and instill as an integral role into our church community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Online Sermons&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A major addition to the website is access to the sermon recorded every week. We love the idea that we are able to provide a continued library of inspirational sermons for our community. Under the sermon tab above, you will find a page devoted to the inventory of the sermons. All you need to do is select the month you are looking for and choose the sermon you would like to listen to. As the speediness of the website is of large concern for our team, we intended on moving sets of past sermons to our Soundcloud profile, which is a web application that allows us to broadcast our sermons. So if you are looking for a specific sermon and cannot find it right here on the website, follow the button to our Soundcloud profile for our extensive library of sermons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;The Blog&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We guess you have already figured this one out! ;) Our blog will be a place for us to share the ongoings of the church and its community. Please be on the lookout for more and more blog posts by members of our community!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Understand that the website is still very early in development and will continue expanding through user interface and functionality. If you are interested in helping continue the development of the website, even if you do not consider yourself and expert, or even mediocre at web design, feel free to email &lt;a href=&quot;cccwebtech@gmail.com&quot;&gt;cccwebtech@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 06:30:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2015/08/23/Welcome-to-the-New-CCC-Website!.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2015/08/23/Welcome-to-the-New-CCC-Website!.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Code For Christ!</title>
        <description>&lt;h5&gt;So, you want to contribute?&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The website does not maintain itself and we are looking for a group of people, whether young or older, to help contribute to our website. First of all, what does contribute mean? Great question! Contribute in relation to our website can mean many things! It can mean:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Updating / Writing content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adding Photos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Linking Soundcloud sermons&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fixing HTML &amp;amp; CSS Glitches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;And more&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;But I don&amp;#39;t have any experience in coding!&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The beauty of this project is that our website is written alongside a program that allows users who may not have experience with code the ability to get their hands wet! A majority of support of the website will be managing/updating content, but assistance with handling code would also be a plus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You are welcome to join the team as long as your have a desire to learn and the dedication to this learning!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;Get Started! Jump Right In!&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to contact &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:cccwebtech@gmail.com&quot;&gt;cccwebtech@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; if you are interested in contributing to the website! Once again, knowledge of web technologies is not required, but a desire to learn is!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5&gt;About the Website&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some programs, frameworks, applications used during the construction of and development of the website uses:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://foundation.zurb.com/&quot;&gt;Foundation&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://liquidmarkup.org/&quot;&gt;Liquid Templating&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.git-tower.com/&quot;&gt;Tower&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://atom.io/&quot;&gt;Atom Editor&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://yeoman.io/&quot;&gt;Yeoman&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 06:25:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>/2015/08/23/Code-For-Christ.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2015/08/23/Code-For-Christ.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
